

PROFILE

Full Stack Developer and Designer specializing with 6+ Years of Experience in modern design & development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management, Term Management and customer relations.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91 82192 71827

LinkedIn:

ankus.co/linkedin

Portfolio:

ankushanand.com/portfolio

EMAIL:

ankushanand718@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Coding & Programming Gaming Reading Novels Writing Poems & Fiction Content Creation

ACHIVEMENTS

3250+ Subscribers on <u>YouTube</u> Published WordPress Plugin on WordPresss.org

ANKUSH

Web Designer & Full Stack Developer

EDUCATION

Himachal Pradesh University, IN) 2015 - 2018

Completed Bachelor of Commerce Degree with 130 Credits and 6.77 CGPA (A+ Grade)

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, Pandoh (Mandi, Himachal Pradesh, IN) 2013 - 2015

Completed Secondary Education in Financial Marketing Management, earned 80.5% Marks with Computer Applications as one of Subjects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

M/S DrabDigital - Proprietor & Web Developer 2017– Present

Lead a 12 People of various expertise, worked with 61+ Clients on 80+ Projects related to Web Development, Brand Design & Digital Marketing. During the time, been responsible for Project Management, Customer Relation Management apart from supervising and helping the team on execution level.

PixelTrack - Digital Marketing Intern March 2020–Jun 2022

Been in Top 25 Performers out of 800+ Interns, Worked on Various Aspects of Digital Marketing including Lead Generation, Email Marketing, Paid Ads etc.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Front-end web application designing in HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap
 JavaScript
- Backend Programming Languages: PHP & MySQL
- Have Experience with Custom Theme and Plugin Development
- Experienced with Version Control Systems (Git and SVN)
- Confident using Web Design Softwares (Figma, Adobe XD, Sketch)
- Confident using Graphic Design (Photoshop, Illustrator, Inkscape)
- Team & Project Management Tools (Asana, Slack, Trello)
- Linux OS (Fedora Workstations & Ubuntu)
- Experienced in Using & Customizing various CMS Softwares (WordPress, OctoberCMS, Webflow)
- Confident Using Funnel Softwares (Cartflows, ClickFunnels)